{
    "id": "167be1437b9846999dbe88fe032df37f",
    "title": "Relative Pronouns Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I know a man …………………………….. has just been to Australia.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whose",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Show me the road ………………………. leads to the railway station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either which or that"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Here is the doctor …………………………. cured me of Typhoid.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either who or that"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He…………………………. does his best should be rewarded.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Wellington, …………………………. defeated Napoleon at the Battle of Waterloo, was a great general.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "that"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a rascal ………………………….. no one trusts.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "whom",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy ……………………………… you saw yesterday is my nephew.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whom",
                "that",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The man ………………………………… stole the money has been arrested.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "that",
                "whom"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house………………………… was built in two weeks.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "which",
                "that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The news ……………………………… I heard astonished me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "what",
                "who"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}